<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Terns The Bird's Blog of Awesome]]></title>
  <link href="http://ternsthebird.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ternsthebird.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-09-22T15:39:05-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://ternsthebird.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[matt.l & matthew.e]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cursed / Blessed]]></title>
    <link href="http://ternsthebird.github.io/blog/2014/09/22/cursed-slash-blessed/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-22T15:30:42-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://ternsthebird.github.io/blog/2014/09/22/cursed-slash-blessed</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>He knew the curse would only last for a short time; Wizard himself had said so. But that didn&rsquo;t stop Him from enjoying His new arms while they lasted. He did everything he could think of that seemed fun.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>He snuck up on Younger Brother while he was playing Nintendo and smacked him with all his might by flailing wildly. Younger Brother turned himself, while maintaining eye contact with the television set of course, so that the oncoming attack could only make contact with his backside, but not before receiving numerous blows to the face. He surprised Mom&rsquo;s face with His rapidly swinging arms by leaping up on the table while she was eating breakfast and creating contact with His arms on her face just as she drew a cereal-filled spoon to her unsuspecting mouth. Spoon and cereal gracefully arced through the air onto the kitchen floor while Mom reeled back in shock and fell out of her chair. Dad simply grabbed the wildly out-of-control arms and told Him to go away. He ran down the streets, flailing at anyone that he passed, much to their chagrin and temporary discomfort. Nobody thought <em>too</em> much of this, as Wizard caused many strange things to occur rather often.</p>

<p>He caught a glimpse of the girl he liked and ran towards her, her eyebrows raised and face expressed fear as she realized there was no escape. He smiled as he got nearer, and his smile grew tenfold as the fated moment approached; He drew back His right arm and prepared to spin clockwise as rapidly as He could, hitting her with His arms as he circled, but just as He began to unwind, Wizard&rsquo;s curse wore off and His foam noodle arms returned to their flesh-and-bone state and His fist made contact with her face, knocking her out cold in an instant.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Damn,&rdquo; He thought, as He turned back towards home and started walking.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cop - Wavves]]></title>
    <link href="http://ternsthebird.github.io/blog/2014/08/29/cop-wavves/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-29T16:27:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://ternsthebird.github.io/blog/2014/08/29/cop-wavves</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You wake up on a warm summer day and hum a tune as you eat your breakfast.<br/>
You call up your friend, and see if he can hang out today.<br/>
He can&rsquo;t, so you go find something else to do.<br/>
You decide to do something naughty.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>You did it, and feel bad, so you seek your friend&rsquo;s advice.<br/>
He tells you to relax.<br/>
There is nothing you can do to undo your wrong.<br/>
Relax and enjoy the warm summer day.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MxtIXl-mH8g">cop - wavves</a></p>

<p>this song reminds me of a game by terry cavanagh: <a href="http://www.kongregate.com/games/TerryCavanagh_B/heros-adventure">hero&rsquo;s adventure</a></p>

<p>if the song were an image, it might look like this:<br/>
<img src="http://ternsthebird.github.io/images/posts/cop_wavves.png" alt="john, sitting back and relaxing" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
